This is one continuous operating session of Radeon Voice Skill Foundry.
The workbench starts with a clean local data directory.
The blue status badge shows how many trusted compile runs have been durably stored.
I upload the same twenty-point-three-nine second spoken procedure used for the Radeon validation.
Voice Evidence version zero point two measures level, clipping, silence, noise floor, estimated signal-to-noise ratio, crest factor, dropout ratio, and source integrity.
No acoustic diagnostic is triggered, and the source receives a one-hundred-out-of-one-hundred pass.
Next, the transcript and aligned action trace are compiled into typed rules.
The policy retrieves local evidence, keeps P-zero and P-one findings, redacts compensation data, requires confirmation for missing ownership, and denies automatic email sending.
The trusted compile run is written to disk rather than kept only in process memory.
The verifier executes seven positive and adversarial fixtures.
The unsafe paths are tested before promotion.
All seven pass, mail dot send remains denied, BLOCK and REVIEW receipts are issued, and the proof bundle receives a compatibility manifest for the verifier, runtime, tools, policy, skill, and voice evidence schema.
The verified proof is saved into procedural memory with its original action contract.
Exact reuse loads the proven skill without regenerating policy or fixtures.
The reuse counter and measured retrieval latency update immediately.
Now the application service is restarted.
The browser stays in the same session.
After reload, the saved skill and trusted proof are still available.
The durable-run count survives because voice evidence, compile runs, and verification results are atomically persisted on disk.
I restart the service again with a different runtime model identity.
The saved proof is no longer silently trusted.
The skill changes to revalidation required and explains that the model, GPU, ROCm, or runtime contract changed.
The Reuse command becomes Revalidate.
Revalidation creates a new child run bound to the current runtime, reruns all seven fixtures, and produces a new compatible proof.
The skill returns to verified status.
Finally, I download the proof package containing the skill, policy, fixtures, receipts, local evidence, voice evidence, and compatibility manifest.
This completes the full lifecycle from voice to policy to proof, through restart, invalidation, and recovery.