This is one continuous lifecycle session of Radeon Voice Skill Foundry.
The cinematic interface runs against an isolated Node API with a clean lifecycle data directory.
This recording focuses on durability, compatibility, and recovery rather than repeating the GPU benchmark.
Speech and compile results use the repository's deterministic fixtures, while the main Demo V2 shows the real Cloudflare-to-W7900 Qwen three A-S-R and four-B path.
Every durable record shown next is created during this session.
I open the Voice module and upload the twenty-point-three-nine second Chinese procedure.
The deterministic A-S-R fixture returns the same transcript used by the real Radeon validation.
Voice Evidence version zero point three measures level, clipping, silence, estimated signal-to-noise ratio, short dropout, multi-frame burst loss, and source integrity.
The source passes at one hundred out of one hundred, and its transcript hash is stored server-side.
The deterministic compiler now combines the spoken constraints, aligned action trace, and local policy retrieval.
It generates the same typed policy surface used by the live product, including runtime-owned identifiers and safety guardrails.
The trusted compile run is written to the isolated durable store and the interface advances into the Policy module.
The generated policy denies automatic email sending, redacts salary data, opens review for missing ownership, and keeps calendar holds conditional on a due date.
Seven positive and adversarial fixtures execute before promotion.
All seven pass.
`mail.send` remains denied, four governance receipts are issued, and the proof receives a compatibility manifest for the runtime, verifier, tools, policy, skill, and Voice Evidence schema.
The verified result is saved into procedural memory with its original action contract.
I immediately reuse it.
The proven skill loads without regenerating the policy or fixtures, while the reuse counter and retrieval latency update inside the same browser session.
Now the recording controller terminates the isolated Node API process and starts a fresh process with the same runtime identity.
The browser UI remains open and reconnects to the recovered API.
The saved skill, trusted compile run, verification result, Voice Evidence, and proof compatibility all survive the real process restart because they were atomically persisted rather than held only in memory.
The controller performs a second real API restart, this time with a changed runtime model identity.
The stored proof is not silently reused.
After reload, the skill changes to revalidation required, explains that the runtime contract changed, and replaces the Reuse command with Revalidate.
Revalidation creates a new child run bound to the changed runtime, reruns all seven fixtures, and restores compatibility.
I confirm the skill is verified again, open the new Proof module, and download its package.
The ZIP contains the skill, least-privilege policy, fixtures, receipts, retrieved evidence, source-bound Voice Evidence, compatibility manifest, and parent-child proof lineage.
This completes voice to policy to proof, through restart, invalidation, and recovery, in one continuous session.