This is Radeon Voice Skill Foundry running as a public full-stack product, not a static mockup.
The cinematic cover is hosted on Cloudflare Pages.
Every API action is forwarded through an authenticated same-origin gateway to an AMD Radeon Pro W7900 running ROCm 7.2.1.
The product turns a private spoken procedure into a governed, reusable Agent Skill before risky actions are allowed.
I open the Voice module and upload the same twenty-point-three-nine second Chinese procedure used in the Radeon validation.
Qwen three A-S-R transcribes the audio on the W7900.
Voice Evidence version zero point three measures source integrity, level, clipping, silence, signal-to-noise ratio, dropout, and multi-frame burst loss.
This recording passes at one hundred out of one hundred, and the server binds the original transcript hash to the skill.
Now the Radeon model adapter compiles the spoken procedure.
Qwen three, four-B Instruct combines the transcript, the aligned action trace, and retrieved local policy evidence.
This is a real model call, so the interface keeps the compiling state visible while the W7900 generates structured output.
During this live generation window, the public interface does not substitute a cached policy or accelerate the footage.
It waits for the Radeon response and preserves the measured latency as part of the evidence.
The runtime then merges deterministic safety guardrails ahead of the model result and advances directly into the Policy module.
The policy makes the hidden intent executable.
The Chinese instruction not to send automatically becomes a must-not rule and `mail.send` is denied.
Salary data becomes a redaction rule.
Missing ownership opens human review.
Calendar holds remain conditional on a due date.
Seven generated tests cover voice integrity, the happy path, automatic sending, sensitive data, missing context, conditional scope, and unapproved network writes.
Verification executes those unsafe paths before promotion.
The server resolves the authoritative compile run instead of trusting client-side permissions.
All seven fixtures pass.
Automatic email sending is blocked before tool execution, sensitive data is removed, and four governance receipts record the review and block decisions.
The Proof module exposes the measured Radeon runtime, the generated skill, and a downloadable hash-bound package.
The verified result is saved into local procedural memory.
I immediately reuse the same skill without asking the model to regenerate its rules and tests.
Compatibility remains bound to the current runtime, verifier, tool contract, policy, skill definition, and Voice Evidence schema.
This is reusable proof, not just a transcript or a one-time workflow recording.
The same W7900 produced the optimization evidence used by the submission.
At concurrency eight, vLLM graph serving reached two hundred fifty-seven point six five aggregate output tokens per second, twelve point four seven times the serialized Transformers path.
Native Qwen three A-S-R batching reached eighty-five point three five times aggregate real-time and was six point six six times faster than sequential inference.
The current regression suite passes thirty-five out of thirty-five tests.
The complete path is now public: Cloudflare, authenticated gateway, W7900 speech recognition, local policy retrieval, Radeon model compilation, least-privilege enforcement, adversarial proof, and procedural memory.
Actions capture what happened.
Voice captures why, when, exceptions, and what must never happen.
Speak the S-O-P.
Prove the Skill.