Radeon Voice Skill Foundry turns a private spoken operating procedure and a real action demonstration into a reusable, governed Agent Skill.
The public interface runs on Cloudflare, while speech recognition and skill compilation run locally on an AMD Radeon Pro W7900 with ROCm 7.2.1.
I provide the SOP, then perform the six required actions.
Each action is accepted and stored by the server before the interface advances: open the review, filter critical findings, confirm the responsible commitment, prepare drafts, create tentative holds, and export the redacted report.
No irreversible mail or calendar action is executed.
The server sends the original evidence to Qwen3-ASR and Qwen3 on the W7900.
The compiler converts intent and action trace into typed constraints, allowed capabilities, denied capabilities, tests, policy, and a GAIA-compatible `SKILL.md`.
The original transcript hash remains bound to the result.
Sandbox Replay v1 now exercises the generated contract.
Positive fixtures must complete the workflow, while adversarial fixtures attempt unsafe behavior.
`mail.send` stays denied, sensitive values remain redacted, and the report uses approved aliases.
The verifier packages receipts and artifact hashes into a reproducible proof bundle.
Before promotion, the product compares this candidate with the currently promoted skill.
It surfaces permission changes, runtime compatibility, proof status, and workflow impact.
Promotion is an explicit proof-bound governance decision, not an automatic side effect of generation.
The promoted decision appears in the Governance Audit Ledger.
Every event has a monotonic sequence, previous hash, payload hash, and entry hash.
The ledger reconciles its events with the receipts embedded in procedural memory.
Mutation or deletion makes the ledger invalid and blocks further governance actions.
The complete chain is exportable as JSONL.
When the same intent returns, the foundry resolves the identical promoted skill, preserves its action contract, and records exact reuse evidence instead of replanning from scratch.
Changed intent does not take this shortcut; it must compile and verify again.
The final path is voice, server-authoritative demonstration, Radeon inference, least-privilege policy, adversarial proof, impact-aware promotion, tamper-evident governance, and exact reuse, delivered through one stable public product.
Terminology boundary: SKILL.md is portable Agent Skill Markdown; no external GAIA conformance is claimed. "Proof-bound" means checked against the current SHA-256 proof hash. Ledger integrity is hash-chained, not digitally signed or externally anchored.